your skill in shatter spin grows more
precise
Cinder I can feel the gong resonate
Inside Me Lord Raz shattering the parts
of my soul that hold me back
M you see that Jordana what smashing
some bases no me becoming the boss's new
favorite there can only be one second in
command
sorry what are you looking at with that
veng stone Medallion we found in the
archive around your neck you can't even
use your pathetic wind powers you are as
useless as your ninja
friends destroying all our storage
crates won't help us save Cloud
Kingdom it's helping me work out my
anger but I don't even think our
Elemental mechs could stop Cinder and
Ros what else we
got there's nothing in Woo's notes the
pages we still have anyway about shatter
Spin and I can't find anything about
these forbidden five Ras wants to bring
back either it's like it was all
scrubbed from history well someone
stopped the Forbidden fight before we
have to figure out how they did it
[Music]
fast heads up Sora
sorry kind of lost control there I get
it Aaron we're all on edge losing that
battle was crushing I'm trying to be
helpful by building useful gadgets but
it probably won't make a difference yeah
I'm training cuz I just don't know what
else to do why are you practicing in
here and not in the courtyard because
Lloyd is out there meditating on his
Visions if he doesn't come up with a way
to stop raw and shatter spin I don't
know what we're going to do
[Music]
l in me I know so much see Together We
will
rise we
F be Ninja
[Music]
I've been here for hours and nothing why
do I have visions of everything that can
go wrong but none about how to make it
right Source dragons are you out there
can you hear me is this just a game to
you I need answers
[Music]
this is the
Mortal the one who released me from my
captivity yes he wields an element who
Among Us claims him is one of mine a
descendant of the
first I sense Danger from The
Mortals coalesence or Not The Mortals
cannot touch
us I thought that once before my
imprisonment H this Mortal doesn't seem
like much to me he was conduit to my
unbridled energy a mortal exposed
directly
the effects could be profound he is no
ordinary mortal and he asks for help you
know as well as I we do not involve
ourselves directly in Mortal Affairs I
ask you to
reconsider he liberated me from my
prison I am in his debt perhaps we all
are very well we shall start him on the
path but the journey has to be his
own what in the
[Music]
FL I saw a vision of I think they were
the source dragons kind of but but I
can't they filled my head with like
piece of a puzzle it's tooo much to
process there was a metal gate a place
we can learn a teacher to seek
out are you sure this is on the level
you've been out here all night and I no
this was
real I mean I believe it was I think
there's an old Master out there who can
teach us how to fight shatter spin
that's
amazing if it's true we sure it's true
as sure as I can be right
[Music]
now Kai time for an adventure yes what
took you so long
ow I'm fine my leg doesn't even
hurt you need more time to let your body
heal the rest of us are going on a
mission so without me that's the
stupidest thing I ever heard who's going
to save all of you if I'm not there
Wildfire there's no shame in getting
injured if you want to be a ninja you
need to stay and rest it's for your own
good
cool you better be going on a super
boring
Mission totally the boringest
[Music]
the Bounty will be all set soon but set
for where I only have a sense of how to
find this hermit teacher like I'll know
when we get
there this is ridiculous isn't it would
Master woo take us on a mission based on
half understood dreams none of us know
what Master woo would do
we're in new territory
here don't worry everyone ninja Zayn
will be here in case any emergencies
arise and I personally assure that the
monastery will stay in tiptop shape
while you're gone uh Mr frohickey also
keep an eye on Wildfire for me but don't
let her know you are cuz she thinks she
can do everything herself count on it I
have a batch of feted swamp tea in The
Cauldron right now beted swamp te I'm
not sure that counts as taken care but
[Music]
okay Lord Roz I have found the location
of the final component your aptitude for
the mystical Arts is growing
Jordana I have learned much from the
hidden Scrolls and your mentorship
excellent we leave
immediately there can only be one second
in command
[Music]
sorry the motor hasn't been used for
hundreds of years the monks just let the
kingdom drift wherever Destiny would
have them go fools turn the engine
I hear steering a ship is a little
easier with your eyes open what's wrong
the previous Visions I had were like
nightmares this one was like an
instruction I could see a metal gate
sense a teacher we need to find and feel
a direction to go but I'm still on edge
I'm not sure I trust what's in my own
brain I don't trust your Visions either
but I trust you the legendary green
ninja has never let us down you and I
have seen so many battles I know you can
handle yourself but if I'm leading us
into a trap what about the younger ones
[Music]
they're not
ready they might surprise you and I
don't think they'd rather be anywhere
else not a good sound to hear coming
from the engine
compartment sounds like the rotor
slipped the drive
belt and now it sounds like the rotor
sned which they can't do I'm assuming
right yeah not a standard
[Music]
part Wildfire what are you doing here
good news I'm all
better what part of stay and heal was
hard to understand the part where
staying and healing is
boring how'd you get past Mr froi I came
up with the plan so cunning so original
that no one else could ever have thought
of it did you stack a bunch of rocks
under a blanket to make it look like you
were in there
sleeping how could you possibly know
that we have to take her back too late
why because it looks like we're
[Music]
here we supposed to go in there Lloyd
yes I think so
[Music]
I ever tell you about the time I was
little and broke down the family vacuum
cleaner so I could build a robot to do
my chores yeah then it turned out your
chore for the week was to vacuum the
house and no more vacuum cleaner when my
mom found out she was so mad so I ran
off into the tunnels under Imperium I
went so far down I got lost for 2 days
how'd you get out that's not important
but let's just say it was gross my point
is I didn't want to be found so I hid
away in the most impossible place I
could find so so this teacher Lloyd
wants to find if they're all the way out
here maybe they don't want to be found
[Music]
that's the place or a place at least
every place is our place no I mean I saw
it in my vision I think it means we're
on the right path we should go up not in
the bounty we shouldn't the ship's too
big to
fit that we could squeeze through that's
probably what the captains of those
ships thought
too so maybe we're not squeezing through
any other ideas as a matter of
fact
woohoo when did you make
these after we got back from cloud
Kingdom Lloyd said he wanted to Grapple
like aand I thought they'd be cooler if
we could use our elemental powers with
them
fun
right even without elemental powers it's
still
cool sweet but two
problems we got a dragon that can't
fly no offense buddy just the truth and
we also have an injured ninja who was
expressly told to stay home who came
along
irresponsibly who's he talking
about good points then maybe it's time
for a little Elemental tech
[Music]
power nice and it comes in my color
you two okay out there I guess my turn
to Pilot yet as
if this is feeling
right and you were worried we might not
be able to trust
your m
[Music]
I'm coming Aaron don't move not a
problem Aaron I'm coming in
hot or
not let's see how these things handle
Spinjitsu
a
yes oh this thing's trying to make me a
lot thinner Sora I can't do Spinjitsu to
help up
K Hey kid nice of you to drop by
aarin I'm sorry I tried everything I
could I just don't know Spinjitsu it's
okay I don't have elemental powers maybe
that's why together we make such a good
team so where do your feelings tell you
we need to go next I believe the teacher
we're looking for is through there
and there aren't going to be deadly
tentacles grabbing Us in there I didn't
say
[Music]
that how can it be so dark in here the
cave mouth is right behind
us huh I got this time to
[Music]
shine is it still getting darker darker
darker technical difficulties I'll have
us back in a
sec there you go hey where'd everyone
go
what Sora Lloyd is that
[Music]
you Mom Dad why haven't you found us
Aaron are the Ninja your family now
instead of us did you forget us what no
I love you I miss
you Kai how did you get so far
ahead wait how did
[Applause]
[Music]
hello can anyone hear me of course they
can't they're
lost Master woo where did you your team
needed strong leadership and did not
receive it but I had these visions
and I blame my self nephew I felt you
were ready to take over for me but I was
wrong you will never be good
enough Jay Jay I found
you huh who are you haha your sense of
humor is still terrible
how'd you even get here stop acting like
you know me I've never seen you before
in my life what Jay don't you dare tell
me
wait this isn't happening is it
[Music]
[Applause]
what even are
[Music]
you you all didn't see what I saw did
you no I think I saw my own thing file
that under the absolute worst what was
in your vision the wasting
nothing never mind I don't want to talk
about
it how did you know it wasn't real I saw
Jay the love of my life but he didn't
know who I was I know the real Jay could
never forget me it couldn't be
real we should keep moving who knows if
that thing is coming back maybe with
even uglier
friends light over there
[Music]
I can't see anything now what the
teacher we're seeking I feel like he's
just through here just through what
could be a massive drop into nothingness
you sure the source dragons wouldn't
have put us through all this just to
reach a dead end I'm pretty sure I think
then it's time for a leap of faith wait
I'm not 100% sure of Lloyd I'm sure we
trust you and you should trust you too
complete
agree Ninja
Go Kai Kai did Kai just leap to his
where is everyone get over
here I knew he was
[Music]
fine that's the midle gate for my vision
we did it we're here
the teacher who can help us learn to
defeat shatter spin should be right
behind her
[Music]